### Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/nolannguyen-4573b4233 (LinkedIn) dribbble.com/NolanNguyen311096 (Portfolio)

Top Skills
Icon Animation
UI/UX Designer
Video Editing

# Nolan Nguyen

UI/UX Designer, Video Editor, 2D Animation Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

## Summary

I'm a creative professional skilled in UI/UX design, video editing, and 2D animation. My passion is enhancing user experiences and crafting engaging content. I excel in intuitive interfaces, captivating videos, and imaginative animations, always aiming to exceed expectations.

## Experience

#### Tevi

UI/UX Designer, 2D Animation, Video Editor July 2022 - Present (2 years 9 months)

Vietnam

Tevi is a technology company, focuses ondeveloping livestreaming platform for contentcreators. Over 1 year working here, I havecultivated and accumulated experiences

such as:

- \* Build livestream UI for mobile & Webplatforms
- \* Exchange UX team, analyze usersand give useful features to users

LynX solutions UI/UX Designer

December 2021 - June 2022 (7 months)

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

- \* Food ordering app design
- \* Delivery driver app design
- \* Building a UI system for the designand development team
- \* Exchange UX team, analyze usersand give useful features to users

#### **VINFAST**

Printed Circuit Board Design Engineer November 2019 - December 2021 (2 years 2 months) Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

I am a PCB design engineer working in an outsourcing position

Viettel Network Technologies Center - VTTEK Printed Circuit Board Design Engineer December 2018 - December 2019 (1 year 1 month)

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

## Education

Eggcademy

Excellent · (May 2021 - September 2021)

HCM University Of Technology (HUTECH)

Good, Mechanical Engineering · (September 2014 - September 2018)